# MIGUEL GUILLAMON

Entrepreneurship + Digital Marketing

#### ELIGIBLE TO WORK IN US | VISA J1

(+34)696724787

MIGUELGUILLAMON1@GMAIL.COM
SKYPE | MIGUELGUILLAMON1

#### **PROFILE**

Results-focused entrepreneur, with a passion for Digital Marketing, specialising in PPC campaigns. Proven ability to drive sales and increase brand awareness. International mind set, having lived professional and learning experiences in Spain, US and Australia.

#### SKILLS

Email Marketing
Social Media
PPC Campaigns
SEO
Wordpress

## **EDUCATION**

#### BA MARKETING & BUSINESS

Universidad Europea de Valencia, 2010-2015

### BA INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS

San Diego State University 2012-2013 (1 year Program)

#### GOOGLE CERTIFICATES

Google Search Ads Google Shopping

#### LANGUAGUES

English Spanish German



#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### FOUNDER & MANAGER

Hyps Eyewear, 2013-Present

- Founder and manager of HYPS EYEWEAR: eyewear brand designed for young travellers interested in design and retro lifestyle products.
- Omni-channel brand: E-commerce, Optic Stores, Fashion Retailers.
- Business plan + brand and logo design
- Digital Marketing: Google Ad words,
   Facebook Ads, SEO, Affiliate, and
   Influencer marketing.
- Offline: store visits, cold calls, business fairs.

#### DIRECTOR OF PRODUCTION

The Feelms 2015-Present

- Production of visual content and online campaigns for tourism promotion.
- Up to \$70,000 budget management
- Client prospecting, creative proposal, pre-production, casting, production and reporting results.

# FREELANCE MARKETING CONSULTANT

LaBocaTeLía, 2016-2017

Marketing Plan 2017 development for franchise fast food restaurants LaBocaTeLía (4 restaurants).